Thank goodness Nezuko's asleep.
Hushabye...
Nezuko!
Stop it!
Baby bunny on the hill...
Tell me why your eyes are so very red...
You sleep tight now.
I can still fight.
I can still move.
This time...
I'm going to fight to the end!
To the very end!
EPISODE 8:
GATHERING
Huh! This really pisses me off.
You're good-looking,
you have three wives,
and on top of that,
you're full of swagger.
You're different, aren't you?
You're not like any of the other Hashira
I have killed.
You must've been special
since the day you were born.
A chosen talent, right?
That makes me so jealous!
I need you to die as soon as possible!
Talent?
Do I look like someone with any talent?
If someone like me gives that impression,
you really are living a blessed life.
You may be centuries old, but if you've stayed
shut up inside a place like this...
I guess you can't help
being ignorant of the real world.
UPPER SIX
What do you know about it?
I know, all right.
But you have no clue, do you?
See, this country is vast.
It's teeming with people
who'd blow your mind.
Some are complete enigmas.
Some can take up a sword
and become a Hashira in two months.
DESTROYER
OF DEMONS
Me, chosen?
Don't give me that crap!
Just how many lives do you think
I've let slip through my fingers until now?
That's right.
I can't be like Rengoku!
Then how do you explain it?
UPPER SIX
My Blood Sickles
are drenched with deadly poison,
yet you simply refuse to die!
I come from a line of shinobi. I've become
resistant, so poison doesn't work on me.
The shinobi were wiped out
back during the Edo Period!
Don't give us that crap!
That's no lie.
The shinobi exist.
I had nine brothers and sisters.
Seven of them died
by the time I turned 15.
Panicked by our clan's decline,
my father, just like a man possessed,
forced us to submit to brutal training,
and the only survivors were myself
and my brother, who was two years younger.
My brother was exactly like my father.
The same mindset,
the same mannerisms as my father...
His subordinates were pawns.
His wives were expendable
so long as they produced heirs.
No one else ever had any say.
Resolutely indifferent.
And I...
didn't want to become like him!
It's hard, isn't it, Tengen?
The path you have chosen.
Rejecting the values that shape you,
that were instilled in you during your childhood,
even as you place yourself on the battlefield...
That's surely agonizing.
Carrying all that conflict
and quandaries inside yourself...
You still...
All of you still persist in moving forward
and battling on. Isn't that right?
So that you can protect
other people's lives.
Thank you.
You're a remarkable child.
I'm the one who should be grateful.
Master, for your sake, I'd never think twice
about laying down my life.
I can surely accomplish everything.
Those who have baggage like conflict
or quandaries are spineless fools.
That's always been the story of my life.
Huh?
What the hell are you laughing about?
The poison's affecting you, after all!
Slowly but surely!
Claiming it didn't work on you was just bravado!
Pretty humiliating, huh?
Oh no! It has absolutely no effect on me!
Wanna see me dance?
I'm so on fire, I could eat 100 bowls
of tempura udon!
In a flashy way, that is!
Don't you dare kick my little sister!
You scumbag!
Well, those are unique explosions.
They can inflict damage on a demon's body
and explode with the slightest friction
from a strike.
She got hit because she slashed one
without realizing that.
She's always taking a hit, that one!
The blade is extend—
He's holding onto the tip of his sword!
What kind of insane grip does he have?
Go!
Damn, I botched the chance
to finish off this one!
He beheaded me again!
Damn you! Damn you!
I'll make you pay for this!
Not fair! Not fair! Why am I the one
who's always getting beheaded?
Hold on. You're onto us, aren't you?
About what?
Not that finding out about us
will do you any good!
Since you're going to die
a slow and steady death, anyway!
Even as we speak, we're creeping
toward victory, aren't we?
I don't know about that!
Better not forget me!
Not only yours truly, Lord Inosuke,
but his minion is here, as well!
Who the hell are these guys?
Huh?
DESTROY
If you're wounded, come this way!
Everyone else, please flee from here!
Huh.
Hey, you guys...
Talk about flashy entrances!
That's what I like to see!
DEMON SLAYER: KIMETSU NO YAIBA
ENTERTAINMENT DISTRICT ARC
You can summon
all the underlings you want...
but there'll still be no blissful future
waiting for you!
You're all going to die, anyway...
so stop staring
with those sparkling eyes!
There are two demons now.
How did that happen?
Also, the Belt Demon isn't dead!
Are they both Upper Six?
Splintered off from each other?
If that's the case...
the main unit has to be this man!
His scent is different!
The weight of his scent!
It feels like the back
of my throat's gone numb!
My hands are shaking!
I wonder if it's from fatigue.
Or...
is it fear?
No!
Even so, I...
We...
We're going to win!
Us the Demon Slayers!
No way can you win!
Not when the Hashira who's your only hope
is ravaged by poison!
Poison?
Oh, we're going to win easy,
you dumbass bottom-feeders!
I'm at the top of my game
when I'm shackled by poison in my system!
Oh, spare us your bravado!
Shut up! Don't you dare
underestimate humans!
All three of these boys
are my brilliant Tsuguko!
They have relentless grit!
Yeah, we do!
Even if their limbs fall off,
they won't let go!
And I've already identified
how to bring you down!
Beheading you at the same time!
Both of you at the same time!
Am I right?
Otherwise, there'd be no reason
to disperse your respective skills
rather than assimilating
your weak sister into yourself!
Easy-peasy, you two!
I see! It's that simple!
We've as good as won, huh?
All those Demon Slayers perished
because they couldn't do that simple thing.
Not even the Hashira!
Fifteen for me and seven for my sister.
That's how many we've devoured!
You heard him!
Not a single one lived to see daybreak!
Long nights are always on our side, after all.
Every last one of you, just die!
Zenitsu!
Leave that worm woman
to me and Sleepyhead!
You two go defeat that praying mantis!
Got that?
Watch your back!
Sure thing!
I won't let you kill my sister.
You! You're the one from...
I have something to say to you.
Apologize to the girl you hurt by pulling her ear.
Huh?
Even if it was your earnings...
that provided them with their basic needs,
that still doesn't make those girls your belongings.
You have no right to do whatever you want to them.
Don't bore me with your stupid lecture!
In what world does someone as ugly as you
get to speak to me as an equal?
In this city, women are merchandise.
The same as objects.
Getting sold, bought and destroyed.
The owner is free to do
with them as she chooses.
Ugly people have no right to eat any meals.
The inept shouldn't be treated as humans!
You shouldn't do the same horrible things
to others that were done to you.
You're wrong about that!
The horrible things done to us...
The things that made us suffer...
We do them back to others
and collect on those debts.
We can never make up for our own misfortune
unless we collect it from the blessed.
Because that's the way we live our lives!
SIX
We've killed off everyone who's ever leveled
false accusations at us, right?
We're going to slash your windpipes
just like we did to the others!
Unbelievable bloodlust!
It's giving me the chills
from my elbows to my neck!
No wonder! You're up against
the Upper Six demon!
Get a hold of yourself!
Uzui's been poisoned!
I have to protect him!
Strike with your sword
the instant he moves!
The second he moves even an inch!
In that instant!
Swing it! Swing your sword!
Evade it! Evade it!
Bend backward! Bend—
What are you doing?
He protected you instead,
and now you're a hindrance!
Tons of Belts from up above!
Huh? Three eyes?
I can see everything!
All of your movements!
Now that my brother's awake,
what you're seeing now
is my true power!
Shut up! Stop screeching
in that damn shrill voice!
Them being your Tsuguko was a lie, right?
Your movements are so out of sync!
What a total bust!
You can't even get close to me!
Shut up, Worm Woman!
If you want to prove anything, why don't you
shut your trap and see if you can kill us!
All right, as you wish!
You can just die!
So quick!
He really is like a praying mantis!
What's up with these slashes?
There's no way out of this!
Heavy! These slashes are so heavy!
Sidestep it! Ward off the blow!
If you take the blow head-on,
it'll snap your blade in two!
If it's power versus power,
the weaker side always loses!
Don't misjudge the flow of power
and ward it off as you should!
The flexible Water Breathing technique
is better for defense...
if it's only to ward off the blow!
My blade never would've gotten nicked!
Sound Breathing...
Fifth Form...
String Performance!
You can assault me with your noisy moves,
but it'll do you no good!
Die! Die! You ugly toads!
It's not just the Belts!
Now we have blood blades flying toward us!
What's going on?
I can't get near that Worm Woman!
Dammit!
These blood blades are big trouble!
I can feel it all over my body
that just a scratch would be deadly!
Damn!
Be useful! Don't let him attack as much!
Find a way to win!
He's not going to hold up much longer!
It's a miracle that he can still move at all!
That shoulder wound must be really deep!
He seems to have stopped the bleeding,
but it's touch and go!
That left hand tied to his hilt
is the only thing keeping his sword in his grip!
All because I got poisoned!
I have to take care of this,
or we'll be wiped out!
I can't breathe!
This furious attack is leaving me gasping!
I'm about to black out!
I have to find a way...
to start Recovery Breathing!
What are those?
Kunai?
It's going to be a pain, dealing with this
much of them in front of a Hashira.
What a chore! So annoying!
When there are still
three fledgling Demon Slayers, too!
Well, even if they hit me,
those things are no...
No.
Would they really try to pull off
such a meaningless attack?
Blood Demon Art...
Rampant Arc Rampage!
He's creating a dome with the slashes!
Hey, hey, hey!
What's going on here?
He's coming at me!
There's one stuck in you!
A Kunai, piercing you, too!
That's right, he's a shinobi.
Not a swordsman.
This guy's always had
otherworldly senses!
What the...
My legs won't regenerate!
I knew it! They're laced with something!
This Kunai!
Probably with something
extracted from wisteria!
M-My body's going numb!
Hey, not too shabby!
Starting to get into sync
in such a short time! Pretty amusing!
Please!
NIN-NIN
Nin-nin!
Rengoku, how would you fight?
I might not be able to handle it
like you would.
I could never be like you, either!
Rengoku!
Your sword skills are a thing of beauty!
Though you do have too many wives!
Look after Young Kamado, the yellow boy
and the boar head boy for me, Uzui.
Just leave those flashy jobs to me.
Next, Episode 9,
"Defeating an Upper Rank Demon."
TO BE CONTINUED